awardspring.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy

## AwardSpring Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to Web sites operated by Scholarship Solutions, LLC (“Scholarship Solutions,” “Us” or “We”), including, without limitation, http://www.awardspring.com/ (each such Web site being a “Scholarship Solutions Site”). Please read this policy carefully before sharing any of your personally identifiable information with us. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.

This Privacy Policy will outline our practices and procedures we follow when handling information provided and collected through our Scholarship Solutions Sites. Scholarship Solutions may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice, by updating this page. You should check this Privacy Policy page from time to time to ensure that any changes are acceptable to you. Your use or continued use of a Scholarship Solutions Site indicates your acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy, as same may from time to time be amended. This Policy is effective as of 11/24/2014.

## What Information We Collect

Information is collected from our users at several different points during visits to a Scholarship Solutions Site.

Contact Information – you may choose to provide us your contact information, which may include your name, company, position, physical address, telephone number, email address and other information. This information may be updated and amended at any time after your initial visit to our site.

Survey Information – When using a Scholarship Solutions Site, you may be requested to participate in a survey. If you choose to take the requested survey, we collect and retain the information you provide as part of the survey.

Cookies and Web Site Information - We use "cookie" technology and web server logs to collect information about how our Scholarship Solutions Site(s) is used by you, to make our site(s) more easily navigable, and to monitor web page activity. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by your web browser on your hard drive. The cookies allow our web servers to recognize the computer used by you when accessing our website. Information gathered through cookies and by our web server logs may include the date and time of visits, your IP address, the pages viewed, time spent at our Scholarship Solutions Site, and could include the Web sites visited just before and just after a Scholarship Solutions Site.

User Communications - When you send email or other communications to Scholarship Solutions, we may retain those communications in order to process and respond to your inquiry or to improve our services.

##  Use of Information

The information supplied by you, or that is collected by us, enables us to provide you information and demonstrations on Scholarship Solutions’ products and services. We also use this information to enhance customer service and our product offerings. As described above, Scholarship Solutions utilizes passive information to learn more about how you interact with the Scholarship Solutions Site(s). This passive information may be combined with other information about you for purposes such as site testing, the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information for internal purposes, and for disclosure to third parties, such as advertising content servers and Web analytics partners. This aggregate passive information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

Contacting You by E-Mail - Scholarship Solutions may use your contact information periodically in order to send you e-mail regarding our new products and services, product demonstrations, special offers or other information from us or our partners which we think you will find interesting. We may also provide you with a periodic newsletter.

Contacting you by telephone, facsimile and/or mail – If you have provided us your telephone number, facsimile number or physical address, we may use this contact information to respond to you inquiries, provide you information or to schedule a demonstration regarding our products or services. We may also send you marketing information in the mail about the products and services of Scholarship Solutions, our affiliates and other marketing partners.

Special Offers and Newsletters - You may also occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, or a newsletter from Scholarship Solutions.

Out of respect for your privacy, you may opt-out of receiving these types of communications at any time by sending an email to privacy@awardspring.com.

## Sharing of Information

Scholarship Solutions will not knowingly sell, share, rent or otherwise transfer your information other than in accordance with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Third Party Service Providers - From time to time, Scholarship Solutions may decide that it is more efficient to use third parties to perform specific services, such as data backup, online webinars and product demonstrations, or the use of external software programmers and software vendors. If we use a third party to provide specific services, then personally identifiable information (such as contact information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for such third party service provider to provide these services. These third party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information only for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by Scholarship Solutions. These third party service providers have agreed to hold and use your confidential information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Links to Other Sites – You may find on a Scholarship Solutions Site links to third party websites in a format that enables us to keep track of where those links may be followed. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Scholarship Solutions Sites that are owned and operated by Scholarship Solutions, LLC. As we do not control other sites to which our site may be linked, when you connect to another party’s Website, such Website is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please realize that we do not control the information provided by you to any other third party site to which you may link from a Scholarship Solutions Site.

Disclosure to Law Enforcement and Similar Disclosures - Scholarship Solutions reserves the right to release your personal information if required by law, in connection with a subpoena, or in the good-faith belief that such action is legally required.

Sale or Merger - In the event that Scholarship Solutions sells, assigns or transfers some or all of its business to a successor or acquirer, Scholarship Solutions may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.

## Our Data Security Procedures

Scholarship Solutions has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of information you provide to us or that we collect. Scholarship Solutions helps protect personally identifiable information by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the servers where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, are bound by confidentiality, and our security procedures are reviewed and revised periodically. If you have any questions about security issues at our site, please send an e-mail to privacy@awardspring.com, and we will try to answer your questions.

## Other Provisions

Modifying Privacy Choices and Opt-outs - Scholarship Solutions users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their personally identifiable information used by Scholarship Solutions Site. You may opt-out from receiving specified types of communications from Scholarship Solutions (such as a newsletter) by sending an email to privacy@awardspring.com. If you have any questions relating to opting-out, please contact us at privacy@awardspring.com, and we will do our best to answer your questions.

Changes to the Privacy Policy - Scholarship Solutions reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to users, other than by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. After posting such amended Privacy Policy, all information thereafter provided to us will be subject to the terms of the amended Privacy Policy. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. Your use or continued use of a Scholarship Solutions Site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy, as amended.

Your privacy is important to Scholarship Solutions. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please contact us at [privacy@awardspring.com](mailto:privacy@awardspring.com)

Alternatively, you may contact us at:

Scholarship Solutions, LLC  
Attn: AwardSpring Privacy  
230 W. Monroe  
Suite 1200  
Chicago, IL 60606
